For many people, flying is a great way to move quickly and easily from place to place.
对很多人来说，坐飞机是一种方便便捷的出行方式。
There are now four billion passengers flying every year.
如今每年有40亿乘客选择航空出行。
The aviation industry has expanded massively in recent years, with the growth of budget airlines opening up new destinations which we can now reach for peanuts!
近年来，随着廉价航空公司的兴起，航空业实现了大规模扩张，许多新的目的地如今我们花很少的钱就能抵达！
But this worldwide appetite for travel comes at a price - it’s increasing carbon emissions, which is harming the planet we want to explore.
但这种全球范围内的旅行热潮是有代价的——它导致碳排放不断增加，而这正在破坏我们想要探索的地球家园。
According to a new study, air travel is one of the things that accounts for eight per cent of carbon emissions – much higher than was first thought.
一项新研究显示，航空旅行的碳排放量占总排放量的8%，这一比例远高于最初的预估。
The US tops the rankings followed by China, Germany and India.
美国位居榜首，紧随其后的是中国、德国和印度。
Dr Arunima Malik from the University of Sydney, who's the lead author of the study, told the BBC that it’s richer people who are more responsible by spending more on high-carbon activities.
该研究的主要作者、悉尼大学的阿伦尼玛·马利克博士向英国广播公司表示，富人应对此承担更多责任，因为他们在高碳活动上的支出更多。
He says "If you have visitors from high-income countries then they typically spend heavily on air travel, on shopping and hospitality where they go to.”
他说：“如果游客来自高收入国家，他们通常会在目的地的航空旅行、购物和酒店餐饮方面花费重金。”
The World Travel and Tourism Council claims things are changing.
世界旅游及旅行理事会称情况正在发生改变。
A spokesman said "We've seen a growing number of hotels, airports and tour operators that have all become carbon neutral so there is a momentum (to change)."
一位发言人表示：“我们看到越来越多的酒店、机场和旅游运营商实现了碳中和，因此变革的势头已经形成。”
Becoming carbon neutral involves carbon offsetting, where tourists pay extra money in order to contribute to environmental projects that reduce the amount of CO2 in the atmosphere – although some say it's just an excuse to continue polluting.
实现碳中和需要通过碳抵消机制——游客支付额外费用，为减少大气中二氧化碳的环保项目提供资金支持，不过有人认为这只是继续污染的借口。
Airline passengers can do this by paying an additional charge when they buy their ticket from participating airlines.
航空公司乘客可以在参与该机制的航空公司购票时，支付额外费用来参与碳抵消。
Things are changing and from next year, airlines will be required to offset any increase in emissions beyond their 2020 levels by reducing emissions elsewhere.
情况正在发生变化，从明年起，航空公司将被要求通过其他途径减少排放，以抵消超出2020年排放水平的部分。
And there are other ways to reduce your carbon footprint when you take to the skies – you can sit in the cheap seats; studies have shown by flying in business or first class “your emissions are at least three times more than if you decided to travel in economy.”
此外，坐飞机时还有其他减少碳足迹的方法——你可以选择经济舱座位；研究表明，乘坐商务舱或头等舱的“碳排放量至少是选择经济舱的三倍”。
You can also travel from your local airport and pack light – reducing the weight of the aircraft.
你还可以从当地机场出发，并且轻装出行——这样可以减轻飞机重量。
But some people might say this doesn’t tackle the bigger problem – and the best action is to take a grounded approach and not to fly at all.
但有些人可能会说，这些方法并没有解决核心问题，最佳做法是务实的做法——选择不坐飞机的出行方式。